

louiecarmona

3D GRAPHIC DESIGNER

+97150 451 7756 louiecarmona@live.com www.louiecarmona.ml



PROFILE

Senior 3D Graphic Designer with over 10 years of Dubai experience in the management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Expert at interdepartmental coordination and communication. Skilled with 3D Design Softwares, Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, Indesign) and other Office applications. Able to stretch the boundaries of creative design to help client's brands stand out.



SOFTWARES

SKETCHUP
LUMION
BLENDER
INDESIGN
ILLUSTRATOR
PHOTOSHOP
PREMIERE



CODING

HTML	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0
CSS	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0
PHP	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
JAVASCRIPT	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0



WORK EXPERIENCE

CUSTARD EVENTS

9 Jumeirah Lakes Towers, Dubai, UAE

2007 - Present

Senior 3D Graphic Designer

Conceptualize and design event proposal.

3D modeling, texturing and rendering scenes needed for the proposal. Creating realistic walkthroughs and still 3D rendered graphics.

Study client's brand for correct application to various design assests.

Provide technical specifications of the design for production purposes.

Working with project managers to ensure correct design is submitted.

Dealing with the clients for various projects description.

Ensuring that all design are compliant with client's standards.

Provide logo design, branding and layout design.

AMED ADVERTISING

Business Bay, Dubai, UAE

2010 - 2017

Graphic Designer Digital, 3D & Designer

Visualize & designs 3d models/mockups for exhibition and events.

Created the magazine template from cover to cover for the company.

Created the corresponding website of the magazines.

Designs and layout magazine pages and covers for the company.

Designs and develops logos, applies to all the collaterals needed.

Maintains and updates websites on regular basis.

Ensure delivery of high standard of work on time/within deadline.

I.T. administration and related support needed in the company.

Established the creative department for the company.

Supervision and management of the creative design team.

PROJECT DUBAL

Dubai Internet City, Dubai, UAE

2006 - 2010

Magazine Graphic Designer & Web Administrator

DOTCOM SYSTEMS - NTDE

2003 - 2006

Graphic Designer / Web Designer



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

3D Modeling
Layout Design
Branding

Website Design Logo Design Motion Graphic





EDUCATION

2000 - 2001	STI COLLEGE We	ebsite Design & Development
1995 - 2000	LYCEUM OF BATANGAS	BS Computer Science
1991 - 1995	STA THERESA COLLEGE	Secondary Education